See the world in a whole new shape.
Behind the Curve is a documentary film directed by Daniel J. Clark.
Meet the growing, worldwide community of theorists who defend the belief that the
Earth is flat while living in a society who vehemently rejects it.
Self, played by Mark K. Sargent.
Self, played by Jeran Campanella.
Self, played by Robbie Davidson.
Self, played by Hannalore Gerling-Dunsmore.
Self, played by Lamar Glover.
Self, played by Stephen Hagberg.
Behind the Curve is a 2018 documentary film about flat
Earth believers in the United States.
Directed by Daniel J.
Clark, the film was released in the United States on November 15,
2018, and for wide release on Netflix in February 2019.
The documentary details ideas of the flat Earth from different perspectives, including prominent flat-Earthers Mark
Sargent and Patricia Steere, as well as astrophysicists from universities including UCLA and Caltech.
It features clips from the 2017 International Flat Earth Conference, held in North
Carolina, US, which attracted hundreds of attendees from around the globe.
The film explores themes of psychology, conspiracy
theory, science vs religion, flat earth.